<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<tei xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML">
    <acknowledgments>
        <acknowledgment>This research was supported by <fundingAgency>the Deutsche Forschungsgemeinschaft</fundingAgency> through <projectName>the SFB 649 "Economic Risk"</projectName>. http://sfb649.wiwi.hu-berlin.de ISSN 1860-5664</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>ACKNOWLEDGMENT. We are grateful to <individual>Dr. G.D. Niswender</individual> (<affiliation>Animal Reproduction and Biotechnology Laboratory, Colorado State University, Fort Collins, CO, U.S.A.</affiliation>) for providing antisera to estradiol-17β (GDN 244) and testosterone (GDN 250).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We are grateful to the personal of <affiliation>UTSW Microarray Core</affiliation> for assistance with these experiments and to <individual>Janet Young</individual> for administrative assistance. We are thankful to <individual>Thomas Südhof</individual> and <individual>Katsuhiko Tabuchi</individual> for a generous gift of Lenti-NLS-GFP-Cre virus. This study was supported by <fundingAgency>the Hereditary Disease Foundation</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>NINDS R01 NS38082</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>R01 NS056224 (IB)</fundingAgency>, <fundingAgency>NINDS R01 NS043466 (SZ)</fundingAgency>, <fundingAgency>the NIH GM59419 (GH)</fundingAgency>, and <fundingAgency>the Ara Parseghian Medical Research Foundation (JR)</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors wish to thank <individual>Ewa Latkowska</individual> for her excellent technical support. This study was supported by <fundingAgency>the Polish Ministry of Science and Higher Education</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>2670/B/P01/2008/34</grantNumber> and <grantNumber>0757/B/P01/2009/37</grantNumber>. The funders had no role in study design, data collection and analysis, decision to publish, or preparation of the manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors thank <individual>Dr. Chunhua Weng</individual> from <affiliation>Columbia University</affiliation> and <individual>Dr. Cui Tao</individual> from <affiliation>Mayo Clinic</affiliation> who participated in the evaluation. The authors also thank the technical support from <individual>Mr. Craig Stancl</individual> from <affiliation>Mayo Clinic</affiliation>. The study is supported in part by <projectName>the SHARP Area 4: Secondary Use of EHR Data (90TR000201)</projectName>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The data and views presented here are those of the authors alone and do not reflect or imply the formal views of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration or any other entity. This study was supported by <fundingAgency>the National Center for  Toxicological</fundingAgency>   . Many of the experiments described in this research utilized a HeLa cell line. <individual>Henrietta Lacks</individual>, and the HeLa cell line that was established from her tumor cells without her knowledge or consent in 1951, have made significant contributions to scientific progress and advances in human health. We are grateful to <individual>Henrietta Lacks</individual>, now deceased, and to her surviving family members for their contributions to biomedical research.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The human seminal vesicles were provided by <researchInstitution>the National Disease Research Interchange</researchInstitution>. We thank <individual>Christine Monfort</individual> for statistical analysis.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>To <individual>Dr Marize Miagostovich</individual> and <individual>Ms Eliana Saraiva</individual> for the help during laboratorial diagnosis and the technical support from <individual>Ms Mariana Lopes</individual> and <individual>Ms Maryrose Lavatori</individual>. To <individual>Dr Joseli Lannes-Vieira</individual>, <affiliation>Department of Immunology</affiliation>, <individual>Fiocruz</individual>, and <individual>Dr Ricardo Galler</individual> for critically reviewing the manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We are indebted to the parents and children from the urban slums of Vellore for their enthusiastic participation and support. We also thank <individual>Drs. Rajiv Sarkar</individual>, <individual>Deepthi Kattula</individual> and field workers for their tireless monitoring of the cohorts and all the support staff of <researchInstitution>the Division of Gastrointestinal Sciences, Christian Medical College, Vellore</researchInstitution>, who made the studies possible.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was done as part of the IDEFICS Study and is published on behalf of its European Consortium (http://www.idefics.eu). We gratefully acknowledge the financial support of <fundingAgency>the European Community</fundingAgency> within <grantNumber>the Sixth RTD Framework Programme Contract No. 016181 (FOOD)</grantNumber>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was supported by <fundingAgency>Carl Tryggers Stiftelse for Vetenskaplig Forskning and Stiftelsen Samariten</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>B. Zeppenfeld</individual> and <individual>A. Daniel</individual> for excellent technical assistance. Antibody against Oxa1p was a kind gift of <individual>J. W. de Gier</individual>, <affiliation>Department of Biochemistry and Biophysics, the Arrhenius Laboratory for Natural Sciences, Stockholm University, Stockholm, Sweden</affiliation>. The research was supported by grants from <fundingAgency>the Deutsche Forschungsgemeinschaft, Sonderforschungsbereich TR-1</fundingAgency>, and <fundingAgency>Fonds der Chemischen Industrie</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank all the employees of <affiliation>the Icelandic Heart Preventive Clinic (Hjartavernd)</affiliation> for their skilful contribution to the data collection. <fundingAgency>The Medical Faculty and the Research Fund of the University of Iceland</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>the Icelandic Research Council</fundingAgency> supported this study.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors would like to thank <individual>Michel Cantou</individual> for the sampling of bivalves, <individual>Enric Saiz</individual> and <individual>Rosa Maria Borrat Padrosa</individual> for providing Paracartia grani eggs, <individual>Maximillien Cuny</individual> and <individual>Benoît Moirod</individual> for their help with PCR analyses, <individual>Maëva Robert</individual> for sequencing and <individual>Emmanuelle Omnes</individual> for histological slide preparation. The present study was supported by <projectName>the GELAMED</projectName> project through a grant allocated by <fundingAgency>the MEEDDM (Ministère de l"Ecologie, de l"Energie, du Développement Durable et de la Mer, France)</fundingAgency>, and <fundingAgency>the Total foundation, France</fundingAgency> to D. Bonnet (<grantNumber>Programme 189 -« Recherche » 18902 C</grantNumber>).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The outcome of this work owes to the entire staff of the <affiliation>l'Institut national de la Recherche Halieutique Morocco</affiliation>. That each finds here the expression of our profound gratitude.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This study was funded by <fundingAgency>the Australian Research Council (DE120101549)</fundingAgency>. We acknowledge <researchInstitution>the services of Metabolomics Australia</researchInstitution> for the analysis of metabolite concentrations and</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was supported by grants <grantNumber>IGA NT 11062-5/2010</grantNumber> and <grantNumber>MSM6198959205</grantNumber>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors thank the following individuals for their contribution to this report: <individual>R. Duran</individual>, <individual>J.L. Martinez</individual>, <individual>B. McKown</individual>, <individual>R. Romero</individual>, <individual>D. Powell</individual> (<affiliation>Portage, Inc.</affiliation>) and <individual>E. Pulliam</individual> (<affiliation>TPMC, Inc.</affiliation>).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>NH, AK, RB: We thank <individual>D. Cicuzza</individual>, <individual>W. Hoffmann</individual>, and <individual>T.R. Wentworth</individual> for their critical review of a previous version of this manuscript. We also thank <individual>D. Gamble</individual> (<affiliation>UNCW</affiliation>) for permission to re-use NH: I thank the individuals and organizations that directly had a hand in the completion of this project; without their expertise, opinions, edits, financial assistance, and permission to access private property, this work would not have been possible. <otherInstitution>The North Carolina State Parks</otherInstitution> graciously allowed me to collect plants from the shorelines of five Carolina bay lakes in Bladen County, North Carolina. <otherInstitution>The North Carolina Wildlife Resources Commission</otherInstitution> was kind enough to grant access to Horseshoe Lake and Little Singletary Lake. I thank <individual>Glenn</individual> and <individual>Carol Lewis</individual> for offering their land as an easement to Little Singletary Lake; they were very gracious, and I thoroughly enjoyed listening to Glenn's stories of Native American artifacts, lake history, black bears, and wildfires. <individual>Dr. Clemuel Johnson</individual> graciously gave permission to survey Bakers Lake Natural Area and I am very thankful for his generosity. <individual>Stephen Clark</individual>, son-in-law of <individual>Dr. Clemuel Johnson</individual>, also provided valuable information regarding wildlife use of Bakers Lake and surrounding natural areas. "Chick" <individual>Gaddy</individual> provided valuable information concerning Carolina bays and associated South Carolina natural community types. <individual>Mr. Gaddy</individual>'s enthusiastic disposition and knowledge of South Carolina ecosystems was very beneficial to this study and I am truly grateful for his time. <individual>Garrett German</individual> provided a wealth of information concerning waterfowl use of Carolina bay lakes. <individual>Rob Richardson</individual> and <individual>Justin Nawrocki</individual> of the <affiliation>NCSU</affiliation></acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Acknowledgments This study was supported by <fundingAgency>the Competitive State</fundingAgency></acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was supported in part by <fundingAgency>NASA</fundingAgency> grant <grantNumber>SSERVI NNA14AB01A</grantNumber>, a <fundingAgency>Jackson School of Geosciences Postdoctoral Fellowship</fundingAgency> to N.D., and funding from <fundingAgency>Peking University</fundingAgency> to N.Z. Computational work was supported by <fundingAgency>Center for Computation and Visualization at Brown University</fundingAgency> and the Pawsey Supercomputing Centre with funding from <fundingAgency>the Australian Government</fundingAgency> and t<fundingAgency>he Government of Western Australia</fundingAgency>. The input files for reproducing the numerical models can be accessed at nan_zhang@pku.edu.cn. This paper benefited from thoughtful reviews by <individual>Andrew Dombard</individual>, <individual>Walter Kiefer</individual> and an anonymous reviewer.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors are grateful to <individual>Profs. Ye.B. Stadnik</individual>, <individual>I.S. Guliyev</individual>, <individual>F.G. Dadashev</individual>, and <individual>I.Ya. Skyarenko</individual> for assistance in performing these studies.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work has been financially supported by an individual discovery grant from <fundingAgency>NSERC (Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada</fundingAgency>).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Acknowl<acknowledgment>This work was nancially supported by <fundingAgency>the National Natural Science Foundation of China</fundingAgency> (No. <grantNumber>81630093</grantNumber>, <grantNumber>81874293</grantNumber>). We thank <individual>Mr Hongbo Zheng</individual> and <individual>Ms Ke Xu</individual> for the NMR measurements. <individual>Ms Yanan Qiao</individual> and <individual>Dr Jiaozhen Zhang</individual> are also acknowledged for the X-ray diffraction analysis.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The excellent assistance of <individual>Susan V. Castro, PhD</individual>, in the preparation of the manuscript is gratefully acknowledged.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The reverse transcriptase was a gift from <individual>Dr J. Beard</individual>. We thank <individual>Drs M. Jacquet</individual> and <individual>N. Affara</individual> for helpful discussion, <individual>Christian Sahuquillo</individual> for his excellent technical assistance, and <individual>Denise Baron</individual> for typing the manuscript. A. F. was supported by a long-term <fundingAgency>European Molecular Biology Organisation fellowship</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Acknowledgments. This work was supported in part by <fundingAgency>National Institutes of Health Grants</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>5P50CA127003</grantNumber>, <grantNumber>R01CA149222</grantNumber>, <grantNumber>R01CA118 553</grantNumber>, and <fundingAgency>National Cancer Institute Cancer Center Support</fundingAgency> Grant <grantNumber>5P30CA06516</grantNumber>. We thank <individual>Dana-Farber</individual>/<affiliation>Harvard Cancer Center in Boston, MA</affiliation>, for the use of the Pathology Specimen Locator Core, which provided data on KRAS mutation testing.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The radar measurements used in this study can be obtained from the Madrigal database at http://jro.igp.gob.pe. The Jicamarca Radio Observatory is a facility of the Instituto Geofisico del Peru operated with support from the NSF AGS-1433968 through Cornell University. Work at UT Dallas was supported by <fundingAgency>NSF</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>AGS-1261107</grantNumber> and <grantNumber>AFOSR FA9550-13-1-0095</grantNumber>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>[25] Acknowledgments. This work was supported by <fundingAgency>the NASA Tropical Rainfall Measuring Mission (TRMM) Program</fundingAgency>. The authors would also like to thank <individual>V. N. Bringi</individual> of <affiliation>Colorado State University</affiliation> and <individual>Bob Meneghini</individual> at <affiliation>NASA/GSFC</affiliation> for their discussions.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The Pennington Center Longitudinal Study is registered at ClinicalTrials.gov (Identifier NCT00959270). Special thanks to <individual>Connie Murla</individual> and <individual>Aimee Stewart</individual> for data management, as well as the many clinical scientists and staff of <researchInstitution>the Pennington Biomedical Research Center</researchInstitution> who have contributed data to the development of the Pennington Center Longitudinal Study. V C 2012 The Obesity Society</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work is supported by <fundingAgency>National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism (NIAA)</fundingAgency> Grant <grantNumber>P20 AA017837 (LEN and CMC)</grantNumber> and <fundingAgency>NIH Metabolism Training Grant</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>T32-DK007319 (DAD)</grantNumber>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We would like to acknowledge the families for their participation and support and <individual>Dr. Dilek Aktas</individual> for discussion. Our work was supported in part by the grant from <fundingAgency>the National Institutes of Health/National Human Genome Research Institute</fundingAgency>, number <grantNumber>1U54HG006542</grantNumber>. Grant sponsor: <fundingAgency>National Institutes of Health/National Human Genome Research Institute</fundingAgency>; Grant number: <grantNumber>1U54HG006542</grantNumber>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was supported by the following awards: <fundingAgency>MRC Milstein award</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>G0801721</grantNumber> (to MIH), <fundingAgency>NERC research grants</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>NE/ J01074X/1</grantNumber> (to MIH) and <grantNumber>NE/M015033/1</grantNumber> (to MIH/BW), <fundingAgency>Norwich Research Park (NRP) Translational Award</fundingAgency> (to BW/MIH), and a <fundingAgency>BBSRC NPRONET</fundingAgency> (<grantNumber>BB/L013754/1</grantNumber>) <fundingAgency>Proof of Concept award</fundingAgency> (to MIH/BW). RD is funded by a <fundingAgency>Norwich Research Park BBSRC Doctoral Training Program Studentship</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>BB/M011216/1</grantNumber> and ZQ is funded by the BBSRC via <fundingAgency>Institute Strategic Programme Grant</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>BB/J004561/1</grantNumber> to the John Innes Centre. The authors declare no conicts of interest. We thank <individual>Catherine Tremlett</individual>, <individual>Andrew Hart</individual> and <individual>Ashleigh Crane</individual> at <affiliation>the Norfolk and Norwich University Hospital</affiliation> for the VRE strain and <individual>Justin O'Grady</individual> at <affiliation>the UEA Medical School</affiliation> for the MRSA strain. We are also grateful to <individual>Dr Jioji Tabudravu</individual>, <affiliation>University of Aberdeen</affiliation>, for his kind comments. KAW would like to thank <researchInstitution>the South African Centre for High Performance Computing</researchInstitution> for access to computational resources.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We wish to express our gratitude to <individual>Drs H.Tanida</individual>, <individual>S.Y.Park</individual>, <individual>S.Adachi</individual> and <individual>T.Hikima </individual>for their help in the data collection at SPring-8. This work was supported by grants for the`<projectName>Research for the Future</projectName>' Program from <fundingAgency>the Japan Society for the Promotion of Science</fundingAgency> (<grantNumber>97L00501</grantNumber>) and for <projectName>the National Project on Protein Structural and Functional Analyses</projectName> from <fundingAgency>the Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We wish to thank many colleagues in hospital and in practice, particularly <individual>Dr. K. Shirley Smith</individual> and others at <otherInstitution>the London Chest Hospital</otherInstitution>, who have kindly referred patients needing valvotomy. We are especially indebted to <individual>Mr. J. R. Belcher</individual>, who has taken an active part in the surgical management of the Middlesex Hospital patients.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors are grateful to <educationalInstitution>the Centre for Chemistry and Biotechnology and Deakin University, Australia</educationalInstitution> for supporting biofuel research. The authors thank <individual>Mr R Chaudhary</individual>, <individual>Dr R Kanwar</individual>, <individual>Prof J R Kanwar</individual> (<affiliation>Medical School, Deakin University</affiliation>) and A/<individual>Prof TTsuzuki</individual> (<affiliation>University of Canberra</affiliation>), for providing the magnetic nanoparticles. The authors are also grateful to <otherInstitution>the Electron Microscopy</otherInstitution> facility at <educationalInstitution>the Institute for Frontier Materials (IFM), Deakin University, Australia</educationalInstitution> for conducting the SEM work.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors thank <individual>Ms. Masayo Tada</individual> for her excellent technical assistance and measurements of serum and hepatic enzymes and components. This work was supported by <fundingAgency>Gifu City Subsidiary </fundingAgency>for project creation "<projectName>Industry-AcademicGovernment Cooperation Project Subsidiary</projectName>".</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was supported by <fundingAgency>Inha University</fundingAgency> research grant (No. <grantNumber>53670</grantNumber>). We thank <individual>Prof. Jin Min Kim</individual> for insightful comments.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors are thankful to Director, <researchInstitution>CSIR-National Botanical Research Institute (CSIR-NBRI)</researchInstitution>, <individual>Lucknow</individual> for the facilities and for the financial support from <fundingAgency>the network projects (CSIR-INDEPTH), New Delhi, India</fundingAgency>. APS is thankful to <educationalInstitution>University Grant Commission, New Delhi, India</educationalInstitution> and GD is thankful to <fundingAgency>CSIR, New Delhi</fundingAgency> for <grantName>the award of Junior/Senior Research Fellowship</grantName> and <educationalInstitution>Academy of Scientific and Innovative Research (AcSIR)</educationalInstitution> for his Ph.D. registration. Award of <grantName>Fast Track Scientist</grantName> to SM from <fundingAgency>DST</fundingAgency> is gratefully acknowledged. <grantName>Award of Emeritus scientist (CSIR) project</grantName> to RDT is gratefully acknowledged.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Acknowledgements. First and foremost, we thank <individual>P. J. Zinke </individual>for an insightful paper that inspired generations of ecologists. We are grateful to Will Pearse for statistical advice. We also thank the authors of the many published studies that we reviewed for this manuscript and two anonymous reviewers whose comments improved this manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Work at UB and UWM was supported by <fundingAgency>National Science</fundingAgency></acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We acknowledge funding by <fundingAgency>the German-Israeli Foundation</fundingAgency>, and the <fundingAgency>DFG</fundingAgency> (Grant No. <grantNumber>SA1031/6</grantNumber> and <fundingAgency>Excellenzcluster QUEST</fundingAgency>).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>B Anderson</individual>, <individual>R Pantelic</individual>, <individual>K Goldie</individual>, and <individual>M Chami </individual>for expert technical assistance, <individual>S A Müller</individual> for extensive comments on the manuscript, <individual>M Kuhn</individual> for plasmid and strain contribution, <individual>K Namba</individual> for discussions and <individual>Martin Jacquot</individual> for support with the supercomputing infrastructure of <educationalInstitution>University of Basel</educationalInstitution>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors would like to thank <individual>Dr Steven J. Hamilton</individual>, 619C89 is a highly cleared drug, mainly by undergoing Woodend Hospital, Aberdeen and <individual>Professor Charles</individual> extensive hepatic biotransformation. Previous studies in F. George, <otherInstitution>Southhampton General Hospital</otherInstitution>, for contributing healthy volunteers showed that no intact 619C89 was patients to this study. We would also like to thank the nurses excreted in urine (data to be published). Even though at the clinical sites for collecting blood samples and <individual>Mr Gary</individual> plasma protein binding for 619C89 is high (# 96%) the Layton for the statistical analysis. plasma clearance of 619C89 is approximately 65% of hepatic plasma flow (1.35 l h−1 kg−1) which suggests that 619C89 is a drug with a moderate-to-high extraction ratio in humans. Second, the steady-state volume of distribution of 619C89 is large, apparently related to a References</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>TGT thanks <individual>Ms. J. Sridevi</individual>, <researchInstitution>CSIR-Central Leather Research Institute</researchInstitution>, <individual>Chennai</individual> for EPR measurements and <fundingAgency>CSIR</fundingAgency> for nan-cial support. SCS and RSS thank <fundingAgency>IISER-TVM</fundingAgency> for computational facilities and nancial support. The authors thank <individual>Abbey M. Philip</individual> for suggesting the possibility of simulating EPR using EasySpin.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This work was funded by <fundingAgency>Istanbul University</fundingAgency> <grantName>Scientific Research Project</grantName> <grantNumber>33202</grantNumber>. We thank <individual>Mr David F Chapman</individual> for editing the manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The present study was produced from the master thesis of <individual>Deniz</individual> YILDIRIM, DVM (<educationalInstitution>Afyon Kocatepe University, Graduate School of Medical Sciences, Afyonkarahisar, Turkey</educationalInstitution>, 2011). We would like to extend our thanks to <individual>Dr. Kürşat KAV</individual>, a deceased faculty member at <educationalInstitution>the Microbiology Department of Veterinary Medical School of Selçuk University</educationalInstitution> for his valuable technical assistance and we cordially convey our deep sorrow for his untimely death and commemorate him with mercy.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The study was funded by a grant from <fundingAgency>the US Agency for International Development</fundingAgency> and technical oversight was provided by <otherInstitution>MEASURE Evaluation</otherInstitution>. Secondary data analysis was conducted with permission of all collaborating authors.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors are supported in part by <fundingAgency>NIMH</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>5R01MH054636</grantNumber>. MBV is supported by a <fundingAgency>National Defense Science and Engineering Graduate Fellowship (NDSEG)</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Supported by grants from <fundingAgency>the National Eye Institute</fundingAgency> <grantNumber>EY03991</grantNumber>, <grantNumber>P30-EY012576</grantNumber>, and <researchInstitution>Research to Prevent Blindness</researchInstitution>. We thank <individual>Dr Serena Fabbrini</individual> for providing Sap-3 isomer.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Author contributions : Dr Yeager is the guarantor of the paper and takes responsibility for the integrity of the work as a whole, from inception to published article. Dr Yeager: conceived of the study, conducted experiments, interpreted data, wrote and revised the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Ms Nguyen: conducted experiments, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Mr Belchenko: conducted experiments, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Ms Colvin: conducted experiments, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Dr Takatsuki: conducted experiments, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Dr Ivy: provided patient access, interpreted data, provided funding, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Dr Stenmark: interpreted data, provided funding, helped draft and revise the manuscript, and approved the fi nal article for publication. Financial /nonfi nancial disclosures: The authors have reported to CHEST the following confl icts of interest: <educationalInstitution>The University of Colorado, Denver</educationalInstitution> has a contractual relationship with the pharmaceutical industry (<otherInstitution>Actelion</otherInstitution>, <otherInstitution>Gilead</otherInstitution>, <otherInstitution>Pfi zer</otherInstitution>, <otherInstitution>United Therapeutics</otherInstitution>) for Dr Ivy to provide consultation. All monies are sent directly to the University of Colorado, Denver. Dr Stenmark has received pharmaceutical company grant monies from <fundingAgency>Pfi zer</fundingAgency>. Drs Yeager and Takatsuki, Mss Nguyen and Colvin, and Mr Belchenko have reported that no potential confl icts of interest exist with any companies/organizations whose products or services may be discussed in this article.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>This research was partially financed by <grantName>the RECUPERA-2020</grantName> (an agreement between <fundingAgency>CSIC</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>Spanish MINECO</fundingAgency>, <fundingAgency>EU-FEDER</fundingAgency> funds) and <grantNumber>AGL2014-52465-C4-4-R</grantNumber> Projects (<fundingAgency>MINECO</fundingAgency>, <fundingAgency>EU-FEDER</fundingAgency> funds). Research of Torres-Sá nchez and Peña were financed by <fundingAgency>FPI</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>Ramon y Cajal Programs</fundingAgency>, respectively (<fundingAgency>Spanish Ministry of Economy and Competitiveness</fundingAgency>). The authors thank <individual>Mr. Bernardo Crespo</individual> for allowing developing our field work in his farm.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>Patric Jern</individual> for critical reading of the manuscript and useful suggestions. We thank associate professors <individual>Ewa Lundgren</individual> and <individual>Anders Liss</individual> for their valuable help with collecting samples. The study was supported by funds at <fundingAgency>the Academic Hospital, Uppsala, Sweden</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Cláudia Maria Valete-Rosalino, Armando de Oliveira Schubach and Madson Pedro da Silva Leite were responsible for the design of the study. Madelon Novato Ribeiro, José Liporage Teixeira and Monique Reis da Fonseca collected data. All authors were responsible for conducting the study and managing data; Madelon Novato Ribeiro, Cláudia Maria Valete-Rosalino, Raquel de Vasconcellos Carvalhaes de Oliveira, Maria Inês Fernandes Pimentel and Armando de Oliveira Schubach analyzed and interpreted data, and prepared manuscript; all authors reviewed and approved manuscript. We are grateful to <individual>Jacline Novato Ribeiro</individual>, <individual>Margareth de Araújo Silva</individual>, <individual>Michele Aparecida Ferreira Moreira de Oliveira</individual>, <individual>Fátima Peres Lima Dantas</individual> and <individual>Felipe Maia Maquieira da Silva</individual> for their help with the patients before the interviews. We also thank <individual>Dr. Sandro Javier BedoyaPacheco</individual> for help with the database. This study was funded by <fundingAgency>PAPES-FIOCRUZ</fundingAgency>, <fundingAgency>National Council for Scientific and Technological Development (CNPq)</fundingAgency> and <fundingAgency>Carlos Chagas Filho Foundation for Research Support in the State of Rio de Janeiro (FAPERJ)</fundingAgency>. Funding agencies had no interference in the design and conduct of the study; collection, management, analysis and interpretation of the data; and preparation, review, or approval of the manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We would like to thank <individual>Professor L. Ernster</individual> and <individual>Dr P. Gellerfors</individual> for their helpful discussion and suggestions, and <individual>Miss B. Persson</individual> for excellent technical assistance. The work was supported by a grant from <fundingAgency>the Swedish Cancer Society</fundingAgency> and by an <grantName>EMBO short-term fellowship</grantName> to F.G.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We are indebted to <individual>Professor G. F. Azzone</individual> for helpful discussions and for reading the manuscript. The expert technical assistance of <individual>Mr Luciano</individual></acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The author would like to thank <individual>Prof. F. Klinkhamer</individual> and <individual>Prof. E. M. C. Abreu</individual> for useful discussions. The author would also like to thank <individual>Prof. U.Tirnakli</individual> for sending reference  [22] .</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors are grateful for financial support from <fundingAgency>the Henan Administration of Science and Technology</fundingAgency> (grant No. <grantNumber>0111030700</grantNumber>). Supplementary data and figures for this paper are available from the IUCr electronic archives (Reference: BV2111).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The author is grateful to <individual>Brian Brush</individual> for his helpful comments and suggestions and acknowledges the financial support from <grantName>the College of Business Administration Miles Research Grant</grantName> at <fundingAgency>Marquette University</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors acknowledge the support from <fundingAgency>the Swiss National Science Foundation</fundingAgency> (projects <grantNumber>137630</grantNumber> to U.S. and <grantNumber>160055</grantNumber> to H.B.). Special thanks go to the technical and scientific members of <researchInstitution>the Geneva and Zurich research groups</researchInstitution> who helped at all stages of this study. H.B. thanks <individual>Peter Hochuli</individual> (<affiliation>University of Zurich</affiliation>), <individual>Jean Guex</individual> and <individual>Torsten Vennemann</individual> (both <affiliation>University of Lausanne</affiliation>), and <individual>Helmut Weissert</individual> and <individual>Stefano Bernasconi</individual> (both <affiliation>ETH Zurich</affiliation>) for long term and highly stimulating scientific discussions.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The author would like to thank <individual>Prof. Dr. Ronald H. W. Hoppe</individual> and<individual> Prof. Dr. H.-J. Bungartz</individual> for the kind invitation to deliver a plenary lecture at the Annual Meeting of GAMM at Augsburg in March of 2002. The content of paper is based on that lecture. The author would also like to thank <individual>Ryuta Suzuki</individual> for discussions leading to a better presentation of the material in this paper.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The last author would like to thank <individual>George Lowther</individual> for the idea of non-linear bounds, <individual>Michael Greinecker</individual> for his hints on dealing with kernels, and other users of MathStackexchange and MathOverflow for their valuable comments regarding measure theory and coupling.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>Pr André Dufour</individual> for his help with statistical analyses.</acknowledgment>edgements. Thanks to <individual>Maria Eugenia Gómez</individual> for finding the original reference of Bouguer's law. <projectName>The DENIS project</projectName> is supported by <fundingAgency>the SCIENCE and the Human Capital and Mobility plans of the European Commission</fundingAgency> under grants <grantNumber>CT920791</grantNumber> and <grantNumber>CT940627</grantNumber>, by <fundingAgency>the French Institut National des Sciences de l'Univers, the Ministère de l'Éducation Nationale </fundingAgency>and <fundingAgency>the Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, in Germany</fundingAgency> by <fundingAgency>the State of Baden-Würtemberg, in Spain</fundingAgency> by <fundingAgency>the DGICYT, in Italy</fundingAgency> by <fundingAgency>the Consiglio Nazionale delle Ricerche</fundingAgency>, by <fundingAgency>the Austrian Fonds zur Förderung der wissenschaftlichen Forschung und</fundingAgency></acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>Michael Heinz</individual>, <individual>Paul Cliften</individual>, and <affiliation>the Genome Technology Access Center (GTAC) in the Department of Genetics</affiliation> for help</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors would like to thank <individual>Julia Stockinger</individual> and <individual>David Schwarzenbacher</individual> for their excellent technical support and <individual>Johannes A Mayr</individual> for comments and suggestions.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors thank <individual>Leonice Lourenço Poyares</individual>, <affiliation>Institute of Biomedical Sciences, University of São Paulo, Brazil</affiliation>, for excellent technical assistance. Research supported by <fundingAgency>FAPESP</fundingAgency>. F. Goulart-Silva is the recipient of a <fundingAgency>FAPESP</fundingAgency> fellowship (<grantNumber>#08/56446-9</grantNumber>), and M.T. Nunes is the recipient of a <fundingAgency>CNPq</fundingAgency> fellowship.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We acknowledge <individual>D Sabatini</individual> (<affiliation>Whitehead Institute</affiliation>) for providing mutagenized KBM7 cells and <individual>V Amarnath</individual> (<affiliation>Vanderbilt University</affiliation>) for providing reagents and advice. We thank <individual>V Vijayan</individual>, <individual>K Amarnath</individual>, <individual>T Peterson</individual>, and members of the <researchInstitution>O'Shea lab</researchInstitution> for advice and assistance. We thank <individual>A Darnell</individual> for critical reading of the manuscript.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The first author is grateful for the partial financial support through <fundingAgency>the French National Research Agency</fundingAgency> (Grant <grantNumber>ANR-11-BS09-0008</grantNumber>, LOTERIE).</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The notion of the third-sector, with which <individual>Michael Dunford</individual> closes his discussion of Lipietz, is crucial to a truly millennial discourse and practice. It is one that has been central in the approach to urban and social development that we put forward in this journal. Can the third sector release the imagination and the vision to which governments, or their current advisers, seem blind? Can the Dome become an icon of what we can, in the new century, leave behind? Meanwhile, William Gibson's bridge, discussed below by <individual>Richard Skeates</individual>, and the now demolished Kowloon Walled City in Hong Kong, present images for the liberated zones, related movements and sympathetic governments-local, regional and national -of the future.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>Acknowledgements. We thank the continued support of the <otherInstitution>Phillip Island Nature Parks</otherInstitution> and its staff and volunteers involved in the continuous monitoring of penguins in Phillip Island since 1968. <individual>Y.Afán</individual> produced the video and improved figures design. Our analysis benefits enormously from earlier discussions with <individual>B. Raymond</individual>, <individual>C. Bulman</individual>, <individual>B. Fulton</individual>, <individual>S. Connie</individual>, <individual>D. Oro</individual>, <individual>M. Genovart</individual>, <individual>A. Sanz</individual> and <individual>M. Louzao</individual>, and with the helpful comments of <individual>Sara Maxwell</individual> and two anonymous reviewers.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <individual>C. Clayton</individual>, <individual>T. Hobman</individual>, <individual>Y. Nagamine</individual>, <individual>C. Ender</individual>, <individual>R. Pillai</individual>, <individual>C. Artus</individual>, and <individual>E. Bertrand</individual> for providing plasmids and/or antibodies. S.N.B. is a recipient of a longterm <fundingAgency>HFSP</fundingAgency> fellowship. <researchInstitution>The Friedrich Miescher Institute</researchInstitution> is supported by <fundingAgency>the Novartis Research Foundation</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We thank <otherInstitution>the ParkLands Foundation</otherInstitution> for allowing us to conduct this research on their property and <individual>Victoria A. Borowicz</individual> and <individual>Scott K. Sakaluk</individual> for assistance with this research.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>We are indebted to <individual>Ms Mieko Imai</individual> and <individual>Ms Tomoko Yamabe</individual> for data management, and to <individual>Dr Haruhiko Fukuda</individual> for direction of the JCOG data center and oversight of management of the study. This work was supported in part by <projectName>Grants-in-Aid for Cancer Research and for the Second-Term Comprehensive 10-Year Strategy for Cancer Control</projectName> from <fundingAgency>the Ministry of Health, Labour, and Welfare (Tokyo)</fundingAgency>.</acknowledgment>
        <acknowledgment>The authors acknowledge grant support from This work was nancially supported by <fundingAgency>the National Natural Science Foundation of China</fundingAgency> (No. <grantNumber>81630093</grantNumber>, <grantNumber>81874293</grantNumber>). We thank <individual>Mr Hongbo Zheng</individual> and <individual>Ms Ke Xu</individual> for the NMR measurements. <individual>Ms Yanan Qiao</individual> and <individual>Dr Jiaozhen Zhang</individual> are also acknowledged for the X-ray diffraction analysis.</acknowledgment>
        </acknowledgments>
</tei>